Okay, we need to talk. And as you might
be able to tell already, I'm visibly
excited by what just came out because
the new claw release, and I don't say
this lightly, trust me, changes
everything. Yes, I know, big claim. Let
me back it up with examples. But it's
not just about the new model, it's about
the applications that use the new model
because both of those got an upgrade. We
have a brand new Sonnet 4.5 model that
is great. But the ability to use this
browser use agent, that's what I want to
show you today. It has the ability to
remote control your browser just through
here. So, let me give you an example
instead of explaining and I'll do all of
that, right? I'll explain to you what
this exactly does, what is in this
release in a second, and then I'll give
you some practical examples and ideas on
how to use this yourself. But the fact
is, we've never seen a browser agent
this efficient and this effective at the
tasks that I actually care about. This
thing is reliable. So, let me just show
you. Okay, so I set up a command in here
which is like slash shorts ideas from
YouTube comments. What this does is it
opens my YouTube studio, navigates to
the content tabs, and opens the newest
video. Okay, so I just gave it this
preset prompt. I'm not touching
anything. It goes in here. It's going to
navigate to the content tab here in a
second. It's going to open up the latest
comments, pull in all the comments,
generate shorts ideas from that and
store that inside of a Google sheet.
None of this is done by me. And I ran
this multiple times and it actually
works. Look, it went to the newest
YouTube video we uploaded. Now it's
looking at the comments. You can see the
entire documentation here on the bottom
right. It's doing the thing. It's
getting the comments. And ladies and
gents, like the thing to understand here
is we've seen many versions of
applications like this. None of them
actually worked. The whole chat agent
thing is nice. It's a good idea. It just
has many hiccups and they run it sort of
like in their own computer, in their own
browser, which is terrible because every
few days it just logs you out of all of
your own services. This thing doesn't
just work more reliably, but it also
runs in your very own browser where
you're logged in. Now, obviously, that
comes with security risks. And yes, I am
on auto accept mode here, so this is
kind of just like running on itself and
I can like talk to you here while it
does it. But my first impression of this
and my second and third impression also
is that it works unbelievably well. It
works so well that it makes me want to
retry every prompt that I've done with
AI and see if I could do it inside of
this little browser extension. Now, if
you follow the channel last week, I told
you about Gemini releasing their version
of it. It's not even close to this.
There has been versions of Enthropics
computer use before this. It was like a
2-year-old using a computer versus a
grown-up operating it right here. That's
how I would sort of express it. You can
see it it filter it for the criteria
that I gave it efficiently right now.
Look, it went to the filter. It's doing
all of this. You can kind of watch it
work as I explain, but there's a lot
here in this release. I'm going to break
it down for you now, but ultimately I
just want you to know that this
extension paired with the new set 4.5
model that just came out from Enthropic
is unlike anything we've seen so far.
And that's not to say that the
competitors are not going to do similar
moves in the near future, but as of now,
this is so far ahead of all the
competition. And we have like a whole
set of test prompts that we already ran
in here and ran in all the competitors
and all the manus and the gen spark
super agent and the chat GPT agent um
using you know all the newest models
none of it is even close and here's one
more thing that you need to consider
like if it hasn't fully landed in terms
of potential if you're not really seeing
why this could be so powerful while this
works let me show you one feature here.
Okay I'm going to open up a new tab and
this is how it works. There's
essentially this browser extension. And
if I go to settings here and then I go
to shortcuts, you can see I set up this
shortcut right here that we're looking
at right now. But the ultimate thing is
hidden here. If you go to edit down
here, you can schedule this damn thing.
So I could have this shortcut that looks
into my YouTube channel, goes onto the
newest video, pulls all the comments,
and then extracts ideas from them run
every day at 4:00 a.m. And now you could
imagine me setting this up for five
different channels that I follow or
like. And then it would look into their
comment sections, collect those
comments, put them into this Excel sheet
as this will do in a second, um, Google
sheet, I suppose, and it would just work
on autopilot. And then you could imagine
applying what I might be doing here for
my content business for every single
other activity out there. Matter of
fact, I ran a little prompt showing me
different things that this could do for
me that I will also show to you here in
a second. But first, let's break down
this release. But I just want you to
kind of like think about what this means
because like ultimately this is the
first time in human history where an AI
can really use your computer in a way
that you would you would be using your
browser with everything set up,
everything logged in, right? And then
it's not just about that. It's that
Claude can now use the browser and
within the browser it can use other AI
tools. So obviously here like I'm using
AI to not just scan the comments but
also write the shorts. I have a second
command in here which is like validate.
Just if I have any fact or GPT generates
something or claw generates something
and I want to validate it. Well, I could
use this little prompt and triple
validated with GP5 Pro. So, if I do
something like that, let's say I'm just
going to open up a new uh window. Yeah,
I'm going to go in here and say
/validate. Now, this is one that you
would not want to schedule. This is kind
of like use as you go. It presets the
prompt right into there. And now I could
give it the information, right? I'm
going to make something up like the US
economy grew by 5% last year. And then
if I give it that, I'm going to say
enter. It's going to go ahead and open
up my other AI tool that I have a
subscription to, which is chat GPT. It's
going to navigate over to the pro model
and it's going to triple verify this
information. Okay, it's asking me if it
should do it. Actually, this is a first.
I I set it to this mode where it just
acts without asking. I would not
recommend that though. Yeah, just to be
clear, but I don't know. Somehow it asks
for confirmation here. Anyway, I'm
giving you the kind of like the raw
functioning of this, right? We're not
going to like edit this so it looks
better than it is. I'm just telling you
from the testing so far, it's
unbelievably good. I think it's kind of
hesitating to work because it's already
at work in this tab. So, you'll have to
sequence these things. But, as you can
see here in this YouTube comment
analysis, it's kind of like done. And
now it's inputting. It's populating this
Google sheet as we expect it to. Okay,
so enough of the demos. I just really
wanted to show you this up front that it
actually works and that it actually
works with the sheet as you would
expect. But what I'm going to do now is
I'm going to give you an overview of
what they have released and then we're
going to circle back to this and show
you a few more examples of how it built
an automation for me, how it runs some
of these different prompts in a way that
wasn't possible before and more. But
before we do that, a quick word from the
partner that made this video possible
and that's Web Flow. So, one of my
favorite things about AI is that
sometimes it feels like you're skipping
many of the steps that you previously
needed. It reminds me of how some people
speedrun video games. You get to the
desired outcome, but you just get there
way quicker. And along the way, you just
get to skip a lot of steps. And today, I
want to show you a tool that does
exactly that. And you might have already
heard of them because it's Web Flow, the
sponsor of today's video. So, Web Flow
is a web design tool that allows you to
do everything that is possible with code
without actually having to write it. And
if you've heard the name before, because
they're the industry standard for
professional websites that aren't
manually coded up. Just a little side
note, a ton of top tier web design
agencies actually only use Web Flow. And
that's for good reason. I would call Web
Flow an intermediate level tool as
opposed to a lot of no code tools that
really aim at the beginner segment of
people that just don't have any previous
experience going into the tool. It might
not be as intuitive in the first hours,
but then the ceiling is way higher and
the potential for what you can make in
Web Flow is crazy. My personal favorite,
and I think this is also the reason why
a lot of design agencies go with it, is
their focus on animations. Some of these
crazy websites where everything is just
in motion and animated are made with Web
Flow. A good animation on your website
can take it from, oh, that's a cute
website to something a professional
designer would charge thousands for
easily. And Web Flow just truly finds
that sweet spot between making these
animations easy to create while still
giving you full control of what you want
the elements to do. This tool is really
what you want to use if you want to take
the next step and go from beginner to
something that is usable in a
professional environment. So, if you're
ready to step up your web design game,
check out Web Flow today. You can use
the link at the top of the description
to get started for free. So, let's start
by looking at the release. Okay, on the
surface, you might look at this and be
like, "Okay, a new model, the benchmarks
are a bit better, looks good. I'll give
it a shot." Um, focused at coders might
be another thing that you're kind of
thinking. And you would be fair to think
that because on all the benchmarks, it
crushes all the coding benchmarks. It's
state-of-the-art. It beats out the GPT5
codeex models. It beats out the Opus 4.1
model, which was Aropic's best model.
And I also have to add this video is not
sponsored by Enthropic, but we are on
the early access list and we had access
to this over the weekend. So, I got to
try the model and I was like, "Wow, this
is it's a great model. It works well,
right?" But what I did not expect was
this clot for Chrome extension that
really unlocks the potential because if
you look at all the benchmarks, sure
state-of-the-art at most of the things
here. But the one I want you to pay
attention to is this one computer use.
Okay, that is its ability to remote
control a computer. And that's what it's
so exceptional at because it went from
like 42 44% to 61. I'm not exactly sure
what the GPT would score here, but let
me tell you just practically from all
the test prompts like the GP agent is
kindergarten level compared to this. It
just works better. And the biggest
weakness even if you find use cases
where it works like well, the biggest
problem with GPT agent and chat GBT is
that it uses like this virtual machine
and it just logs you out of the accounts
regularly. So I remember I even got used
to like ordering groceries automatically
like a standard basket like once a week.
Um, but in week two it just lost my
credentials and it kind of lost the
cookies and it ordered the entire order
to some completely different address in
Lisbon and instead of like five bananas
by piece, it got five bundles of
bananas. So all of a sudden I ordered
like 25 bananas to completely wrong
address, paid for it all, never got it
back. It just messed up. That's just an
example for how it would work cuz it
just loses the cookies and the login
information regularly in your browser.
it holds up way longer because like you
use it on a daily basis and if it loses
that you would even log back in plus it
just works right because it's local. So
that is a big advantage and these scores
just make a huge difference. By the way
this benchmark is different tasks that
you would do in an everyday scenario on
your computer on your browser. That's
what the examples here are. So from
successfully completing like 42% of them
this jumped up to 61%. Okay. So that's
what what I want you to pay attention to
here. Here you can see the different
kind of like areas and it's just better
across the field in finance, law,
medicine and STEM fields. And basically
it makes Opus 4.1 a bit obsolete right
now which is interesting. So if that is
a question in your mind as in like okay
should I be using Opus or Sonnet 4.5?
It's set 4.5 right now. This is what I
want to really go into though. The
computer use and they don't even make it
that big of a deal here. They show two
more things and I want to cover those
first. So they uh launched a clawed
agent SDK. It's basically a new way to
access it through the API that has a lot
of these things like memory. I think
this is really interesting, but I really
I genuinely need more experience with
this to give you informed opinion on
this because this is just something new
that I haven't been able to explore.
These browser agents I've been excited
about since day one, but they never
really worked and this is I really have
a breakthrough feeling right now. But
yeah, this cloud agent SDK just allows
you to do things like integrate memory
into API calls, which is like super
interesting. So essentially there was
like a graph down here that showed it
was it a different tab here managing
context on the cloud developer platform
like essentially you can independently
manage context like this example is
great where it plays katan so you can
like let the API play katan but then
there's like a second context window
that is only responsible for memory and
as like the history of the game
progresses that is not stored in the
main model but it's stored in like this
memory unit on the side as the game
happens it fills the context window but
then at At a certain point when the
context window gets too full and and I
hope this is not going over your head.
I'm not like going too deep here. But as
the context window kind of fills up with
the different see that right there it
went from 150k to 67k. It automatically
throws out all the context it doesn't
need along the way. So it doesn't need a
5 billion uh token context window. It
just reviews itself regularly and throws
out everything it doesn't need. This is
unheard of in through APIs. Yeah. Cloud
code had this. That's where they learned
how to build this, how to use this, and
now they're putting it into the API. So,
I think this is really exciting for the
SDK. I really need like more experience
and to hear from more people to give you
informed opinion. It's basically out. If
you're a dev, you want to look into
this. But what I really want to talk
about today and what I really feel
qualified to judge here is the browser
agent, which is the big release here.
Um, it's this right here, Claude and
Chrome. It's only available on the max
plan and also only I think they said
only a select thousand users have it for
now. I am blessed enough to be on the
early access plan. So I I guess I'm one
of the users and I've been trying all of
these things and more. And again, as you
can tell by the intro of this video, it
just works well. It just works well.
Basically, what this is is it's a Chrome
extension that you install in here and
then you can open it up. You could let
it ask before acting or you could like
let it act without asking. It's kind of
the dangerous just do it mode, yolo mode
as some people would call it. So that's
the overview view. Yeah. And this might
be a good time to kind of hop back into
the examples I started in the beginning
because maybe uh right here it should
have five new ideas. And as you can see
right there, yeah, it found new ideas.
All five comments with their hooks and
script outlines have been successfully
saved to the Google sheet in the short
seeds tab, row 7 to 11. So these are the
brand new ones. Um, I guess if we were
to really scrutinize this, we could say,
"Okay, it might be missing a line here."
But also, we didn't let it work in
peace. I was like doing stuff here. I
remember like during the first run, like
when I started clicking to the side, I
actually like messed it up and I clicked
here and all of a sudden pasted in here.
So, it does like its piece. I'll tell
you that. But what matters is the result
here, right? And like, let's see. So,
the date is correct here. It copied
everything into one field. That would be
a fault, right? Like, let's be clear,
that's not perfect. But here the first
line kind of worked. Maybe here I would
need to work with the prompting
definitely. This is like version two of
the prompt, right? I would need to keep
refining this up here, this prompt with
the different steps. But let me tell you
from this right here, here's the raw
prompt or raw comment. Here's the hook.
Why do AI benchmarks ignore everyday
tasks? And then there's um kind of an
idea on how I could present the short.
And honestly, this to me automatically
running at 4 in the morning is a very
powerful thing. I understand that you
might not be running a content business,
but just think about the possibilities
here. Okay, let's just like zoom out for
a second. I want you to think about
this. Every single prompt that you've
ever done, there's sort of this like
assumption that you kind of accept as a
reality when you use chatbt for a bit.
The assumption is like okay, it's wise,
but it hallucinates sometimes and it
knows a lot, but there is a knowledge
cut off. then like you know there's
remedies to all those things but then
let's move on like there's also another
assumption which is like it can do a lot
it's very smart it has a lot of
information but it cannot use the apps
that I use on a daily basis it cannot
use Gmail it cannot use my calendar it
cannot use Google sheets or word
documents and the solution to that this
far has been one word that made you know
big waves this year and another word
which made big waves a you know
questionable impact for many people's
life. Those two words is one automation,
right? That's the answer to like okay
like LLMs are smart but they can't use
the things that I actually do. So like
let's build automations where the LLM
kind of has access to these various
things, right? Like right here, this one
was actually built by the extension.
I'll talk about this in a second. Yeah.
So if I if my LLM cannot use Gmail, then
I'll just go into here and uh in like
NANE or make or Zapier and then I'll
just build an automation where it has
access to Gmail and then I can do that.
The problem is these flows are like
mostly deterministic. So they go from
one point to the other and your problems
are probably more fluid than that,
right? On an everyday basis, you have
new problems, right? That's the
beautiful and also horrifying thing
about life. like every day presents new
troubles, new challenges and you need to
come up with solutions. That's why
people have jobs. That's why there's
always something to worry about. But
here with this extension, it allows you
to kind of like be a bit more like
water. Whereas automations, they're a
bit more straightforward. Now, the
second word that I wanted to talk about
here that were was sort of a solution to
this like AI is powerful, but my
problems always vary, the the word is
agents. But the thing is like in many
ways they haven't been able to deliver
what the hype is about. And in some ways
they've been incredibly useful, but it's
just like you human expectations around
that word of like who they're just going
to like do stuff for you didn't really
align with the reality of like what an
agent looks like these days. A good
agent for most people is like using the
deep research function in here, right?
That's agentic and it's incredible and
it's very powerful. And also I would
argue like GBT 5 Pro is extremely
powerful and it's agentic, right? it
like has the AI reasoning and and tool
use with like internet access and stuff
that's like agentic and that's super
powerful and also like cloud code and
the CLIs if you're into that entire
world are super powerful yet 9% of the
people don't use claw code regularly and
don't use like advanced automation
workflows with like aentic elements in
the middle but everyone can use a
browser agent where they just click a
button and whoop right there you have
your little browser agent and you can
just tell it to do what you want it to
do and it uses your browser. You don't
need to set anything up. You don't need
a virtual machine. You don't need like a
whole like environment where it like
stores your credentials or whatever. No,
it just uses the browser you're in. And
I think that's really powerful
especially when you've pried with a
model that can actually get things done.
And that's why I think this this changes
a lot. Okay, so this is why I think this
really matters. And now I want to get
into like more examples. Okay, so now I
gave you like the overview of what this
release is about. I gave you kind of
like my thinking of why this changes
things. And now I want you to think
about all the prompts that you've run
and how they would look differently and
behave differently if they had access to
everything on your computer. Because you
know, let's take the most classic prompt
of them all, like writing an email,
right, to somebody. Usually writing an
email is not just writing an email. It's
like gathering a bunch of information
that is somewhere, whether it's in your
head, on your phone, in your WhatsApp,
in your messages, in another email
thread, in a Google sheet, in a Google
doc, gathering that information,
thinking through it, and then
formalizing that and communicating it
through the medium of email. That's what
writing an email is. It's not about the
writing. The writing is the arguably the
easiest part. It's the thinking. It's
the information retrieval that is hard.
Well, what can this do? Well, you could
go ahead and tell it to open up a
specific Google sheet, take in all this
information, or even better, you maybe
have a Google doc where it kind of just
takes that information. And this is
exactly their demo where it goes into
the Google doc. It takes in the
information and it takes the information
and it uses it as context to then write
the email. So maybe if you and your team
have a document that they're
collaborating on with all the details on
some project or some case or whatever
you're working on, then Claude can
dynamically go into that sheet, take all
the content as context, and then use it
to write project updates every day. And
I'm going to show you step by step how
this idea that I've been now talking
about for the past few minutes
materializes into something that you can
do yourself and actually use. Okay? And
I think that's what this channel really
is about. So I'm just going to show you
now. Okay? So, I have a brand new Google
document here and we're going to go
through this workflow even if it takes a
while. I'm going to name it like I'm
just going to call it AI advantage.
Let's say it's a Vibe coding course. And
then maybe it includes uh various links,
maybe it includes uh some context and
maybe it includes uh workflow. So, just
for the sake of this tutorial, I'm going
to take some of the context from the
guide library in our community and I'm
going to copy some stuff over into this
context document. So, for example, let's
take this tutorial on building agents
with plain language. So, let's take this
as context here. Okay, guide info.
This is the context.
This is the workflow.
Right.
And this is we we enter like very
interesting territory here because like
I'm using a guide on what to Okay, let's
let's set up this context document and
name it actually this. Let's rename it.
So build AI agents using plain language
with the NAT agent. Okay, nice. Now all
of that is in here in my Google doc,
right? For links, the links are already
in there. Okay, so this is just an
example again like just imagine like
whatever you're working on all the kind
of like surrounding data is in here. So
maybe some emails that you communicated
or maybe some transcripts whatever like
the context of the project might be are
in here. Okay, nice. So I'm going to go
ahead and I'm going to make sure this is
shared. So I'm going to say share. I'm
going to make this any accessible to
anyone even though that's not necessary
because like I'm working on my local
browser, right? So I could actually keep
this restricted. And now that I have
this document, I'm gonna open up a new
um claude um for Chrome preset and I'm
going to create a little shortcut here.
Okay, I'm going to say slash write um
project update email AI agent. Okay, for
this particular project then I would say
okay write a new email and I'm would
make this a workflow. Step two, write an
email. Step one, open this document and
read all of its content into the
context. Okay. And then I just add the
link in brackets. Step two, write a new
email in Gmail to um I'll just say
eigormyadvantage.com
with a summary of what the document
includes and what the first step is.
Okay, so these two things. So we want
just a summary on what the first step
is. Now you could imagine if you want to
set a automatic daily updates to your
boss, you could just make sure most
up-to-date information is in this
document. And then in step two, you
would formulate this email. And then in
step three, I'm going to go ahead. So
here's a brand new Google document
update or like update archive. So like
email and then date, maybe the other way
around. Okay. And then let's finish
setting this up. So here inside of the
settings, I'm going to say step three.
Inside of this Google sheet, I want you
to track every email you sent. Um,
fields,
date, email or like not fields, what
would this be? Columns. And then that is
sort of it sounds good. So the starting
point of this is this document and also
I need to give it uh the link to this
sheet. I hope this works. I'm doing this
live with you and let's see if this
works. So I'm just going to copy this
link again. I'm can keep it restricted
as this is in my browser. And I'm going
to let this work. Link to the sheet
right here. Okay. So it has everything.
And as you can see like if this works
once I'm going to test it now, but I
could just enable this and schedule it
to run every single day at I don't know
9:00 a.m. like I enter work and my boss
would like or like whatever this email
would receive an update from everything
from within here. And then I would log
the answers into here. Now, this took me
a glorious what was this like 3 minutes
to set up. Sure, I might have a bit of
experience with this stuff, but like I'm
also explaining this to you. And also,
we've been talking about prompting for
like 3 years now on this channel, okay?
So, you better have some prompts at this
point that you can kind of like rethink
into, oh, the prompts can now access my
browser and the stuff actually works.
Now, how can I transform certain prompts
to do stuff like this for me on schedule
as schedule tasks? Okay, so we have this
set up. Now, all I need to do is to test
it is I would go into the agent here on
the side and I need to move my camera so
you can probably see this. But all I
would to do need to do here on the
bottom right is say slash and then uh
write project updated date email AI
agent. Yeah. And I'm going to set this
to act without asking. So this nicely
runs. And hey, if this fails, so be it.
Again, this video is just here to show
you what's possible. But as you can see,
it opened the document. I'm going to
keep my hands up here. It's doing all of
this by itself. It opened the document.
Now it's going to take in all the
context. Good. I see the document is
loading. Let me scroll down to read all
the content in the document. Guys and
ladies, like I cannot emphasize enough
how surprised I am by how well this
works. And I think one of the big
reasons is because they took everything
they learned from Claude Code and its
success over the past months and
implemented that into this new model and
this agent. And I wonder if like the
competitors are even going to be able to
keep up. Well, to be fair, the codec CLI
is also pretty damn good now, but like
seriously, this is so impressive. In
this moment in time, this just works.
So, as you can see, it just scrolled
through the entire thing and it's taking
the screenshots and the content there.
Perfect. I've now read through the
entire document. Now, let me open Gmail
in a new tab to compose an email to
Eigor at myadvantage.com.
Okay, so navigating to mail.google.com.
Okay, so I think it's Gmail is now open.
Let me close this notification popup
first. So, I think it's open in a new
tab. As you can see up here, I I'm even
hesitant to like kind of like move my
mouse cuz I don't want to like trip it
up with that. But, as you can see, like
over there, there's a little like Gmail
tab that opened up next to this one. And
we're going to double check all of this
in a second, right? Pop-up is still
there. So, like it dismisses the pop-up.
One interesting thing that we found
during the testing of this in the
community, I just had an office hours
and like 10 of us hung out for two hours
and really kicked the tires on this
thing. One interesting thing that we
found like on all pop-ups it like
disagrees to share privacy information
on cookies and stuff. So Mike from the
community noticed that as we were
testing. Thanks Mike. And it sort of
like I don't know maintains your privacy
I guess. Also it denies some requests.
So if you give it some like blatantly
false information and you ask to verify
it. It's denied that request which I
thought was interesting too. Anyway, so
it's doing this now, right? It's
clicking on the subject field. I kind of
wish we saw it work, right? Should I
risk it? I guess I'll risk it. Let's
risk it. Okay. So, let me just very
maybe let's time it right. So, like so
it doesn't click in the message body and
compose the email. I hope I don't mess
it up. I I I don't want to like time
this in the middle of a click. So, like
let's it's it's writing right now
clicking. I feel like this would be a
bad time to click. But yeah, like while
it does that and let me let me move over
quickly. I'll tell you in a second what
I think you should do with your existing
chats and prompts like practically to
get to take advantage of this. It's
taking screen. Okay. No. Okay. What's
going on? Is this the tab? Oh no. Did I
mess it up? Let's see. Where is it? Did
we lose it? Okay. Oh no. I know. I
shouldn't have done it. Oh no, we're
back. Okay. So, let's just let it work
and then review it in the end. Okay. So,
it's running here in the background. Let
me give you a strategy for what to do
here really because like I think this is
I know this is this is like a lot. Yeah.
This is like a new release and it opens
so many new possibilities, especially
with the scheduling and the browser use.
But I think what you should think about
is like you should take some of your
favorite prompts and you should see if
there's like apps that you use in your
browser or like do this. Take some of
your favorite prompts on one side, open
up your browser history and look at what
kind of apps you used over the past few
days. Like what sites do you frequent?
Is it Gmail? Is it cheats? Is it other
stuff? And see if there's anything that
AI could kind of like do for you
automatically that you do manually that
would help you. That would be a good
starting point. That's a good starting
point for automation. And I think this
will work here too. Secondly, there's
this trick that you can do where you set
up a project inside of chat GPT. Give it
all the context on something there and
then you let this extension navigate
into the project to do your task. So you
don't need to give it all the context
there. Matter of fact, all you need to
do is make sure that that project has
the up-to-date information and then it
can do things with AI for you. So you
don't even need to prompt anymore. You
just set it up once. You schedule out
the tasks and then it does it regularly.
Realize this is not exactly a beginner
workflow, but this is why learning all
these tools is so essential. It allows
you to set up sort of a a base, a
knowledge base, a task base of things of
context about your life. And then tools
like this allow you to plug into that
and to actually get things done. And
breakthroughs like this will enable more
and more of it. So now it's actively
asking me if I want to send this email.
So, it wanted the confirmation for that.
I'll just say yes. And then let's see if
it worked. And then if it did, I'll show
you one more example here that I did
earlier. And we can end the video on
that. I really wanted to give you
multiple examples of things. And I
wanted to show you our full workflow,
which I think we did here. And now we
can judge it. Let's see if it actually
worked. I can see the email is ready to
send. I mean, and again, apologies. I
wish we could kind of like follow along,
but also like I want to give you the raw
and authentic take on like how this
performs in a browser cuz I realize most
people won't have access to it yet. So
right here I can see the mail is ready
to send with all the content. Now let me
click the send button. Excellent. The
the email has been sent successfully. I
can see the message sent confirmation at
the bottom of the screen. And now it's
going to the Google sheet to fill in the
information. Can I tab over and see it
work? I wish I could. Let's just see it
appear here. So it should be working in
here. Claude is active in the tab group.
It showed me down there. Yeah, the chat
is like kind of tied to this window, but
it should be working in here. So, yeah,
if I want to open the chat, I need to
tab over anyway. Okay, so you can see it
like it disrespected my header there.
Fair enough. It put in the date and the
email. But technically, I didn't tell it
that there's a header. I just tell it
told it like, "Hey, put in the date and
the email," which it did here. So, like
this that's a problemic problem. That's
actually good instructions following
almost, I would argue. You know, sure,
could it take a screenshot and kind of
think about it critically before it did
it? Yeah, but also like could I change
the prompt to make this work also? Yeah.
And I think that's what I asked it for.
Yeah, I asked it to Let's review that.
Inside of the Google sheet, I want you
to track every email you sent. Columns
are date and email link to the sheet.
Okay, so I didn't mean email address,
but email content, but again, I it needs
to be more specific. I was kind of doing
this on the fly. Um,
yeah, I think it did this. Um, I see
that I accidentally overwrote the header
row. Ah, it's reflecting the data is now
in the row one where the header should
be. Let me fix this by inserting a new
row at the top for headers. Okay, so
it's fixing its mistake now. Nice. Look,
it's like inserting a new row. And
that's that's what I'm saying. It just
there's no better way for me to express
this than like it just feels better.
Like sure, the benchmark scores clearly
show that it is better, but like stuff
like this, like look, it just fixes
itself. And then you refine the prompt,
you schedule this to go out every day at
9 in the morning and you have an
automatic project update that you can
send to team members. And all you need
to worry about is not actually updating
the team members, but making sure that
like your Google doc that you work in is
up to date. Great. Simple thing. Okay.
So, I just wanted to finish here and
then I'm going to show you one more
example super quick automation related
and two a prompt that I ran to show me
what it can do for my business that you
can kind of copy and use for yourself.
Okay, there you go. It did that. It It
fixed itself. Let's see what is it
thinking right now. Excellent. A new row
has been inserted. And yeah, this is
looking good. Meanwhile, I kind of like
want to take a peek into my Gmail and
see if this um actually went through
Gmail.
All tasks have been completed. So, see,
read the Google doc. Done. Send email to
Eigor at my advantage. Done. And then if
I go into my sent emails right here, you
can see it. Summary NA10 natural
language AI agent guide. Higgore. So I
asked for two things, right? Like a
summary that is this right here. And
then the first step, the first step
involves downloading into two JSON files
and accessing Google doc template.
Perfect. Perfect. It just perfect. Like
sure, could I like refine it to enter
the data and all the email content into
the Google sheet? Sure. That's a prompt
tweak. But it did what I wanted. Cool.
Two last things that I promised you.
First of all, what I did in here, I
thought this was really cool. I asked it
to do something simple. create an
automation that automatically sends a
email from my Google account whenever I
press a button. Okay, so it created a
web hook. So I could have been more
specific. I I didn't want that which
acts as a button you can press via URL.
Okay, I meant like a different trigger,
but that's fine. And a Gmail note to
send the email. And here's what really
got me and sold me here because this is
in my browser and because this like I
was logged into NAND here, it is able to
like open this like look at this. It has
the OOTH set up already. So this is not
like all the other workflows that create
automation workflows and you import them
and you have to connect everything up
and like 80% of the work is left. This
can do it and everything is connected up
already. So you could even like use this
to automate the creation of automation
if you have that skill. Guys, this is
what I keep telling you like all these
AI skills they stack. Like you learn how
to express your personal context just in
order to understand what prompts would
help you and to get more out of them.
When you have that, you learn how to
build little GPTs, learn how to populate
projects. When you have that, you learn
the very basics. Well, you can go into
more advanced prompting or you can go
into automation. And you use all of the
first building blocks here like your
context to automate things away. And
when you have automations, you can start
like building more automations with
this. Or you can start and do what I'll
show you here as the last thing in this
um video. And I I'm just I'm just
excited. I just can't help myself. But
like the last thing that I want to show
you here is that you can kind of go into
your work context that I teach how to
set up and you can kind of set this up,
right? You can go in here and you can
make sure that you can use a prompt like
this and you can find different high ROI
ideas that work for your company. Now,
this only works because inside of the
project, I have a big document which is
like an overview of my company. I have
my mission, vision, values. I have all
the things that I've taught on this
channel and in the community on how to
set these things up for yourself. And
when you have it, you go in here, you
ask like, "Okay, there's this new
feature. How could I use it?" And then
it's like, "Yeah, number one, you could
do a daily AI news radar or you could do
a app of the week where it actually
tests the app for you." Matter of fact,
I I showed you these guides in the
community. We had this idea of like we
could actually now test all the guides
regularly and then it could create a
Excel sheet or or like Google sheet with
suggestions on what to update, what
might be out of date, what didn't work,
right? So we don't have to test the
workflows ourself like sure we we do it
when we initially created it but like
maybe once a month we could just let
this extension do the QA testing. It
could generate a bunch of prompts of the
week and like evaluate the results. It
could um reply to community questions
for us, right? Like it could go into the
community as it's logged in a man
browser. Um it could test funnels front
to back. All of this along with the
prompt, very powerful prompt right here
that you can kind of like run to see
what this could do for yourself. Again,
this will work only work if you have
like your own context set up. And there
it is. This is really what I wanted to
share with you today. Sonnet 4.5 big
kind of update across the board on
capabilities, but ultimately the thing
that I think matters most for most
consumers is this extension. So check if
you have access yet. It's only for the
max plans, but they will be rolling this
out over the next weeks and months. And
yeah, leave a comment below with what
you think you could use this for. And
with that being said, I can't wait to
like retry every prompt I've ever done
and see if it could use my browser in an
unexpected way to generate more value
for me or save me time or just make my
life more efficient and better cuz
that's what these tools do. And that's
what the progress in the space that is
available to consumers like us makes
possible. Okay, I hope this was
interesting. I hope you enjoy these
examples. I'm going to follow up with
more. This is just kind of my first and
second impression after testing this for
a bit. And yeah, it's really exciting.
You know, if you follow this channel, I
don't say that often. So, I hope you
have a wonderful day. My name is Eigor
and I will see you very soon. Bye-bye.